

Zach Phillips







I'm very interested in learning new technologies. Recently I've worked for a small business providing tech support along with website administration for their business website. I'm excited to be learning new skillsets in development with TrueCoders. I've found development fascinating as it provides a combination of creative outlook and organization. I hope to learn much more and become increasingly passionate as a developer.

- Motivated self learner and detail oriented team player with strong organizational skills
- Experienced in multiple operating systems, computer applications, and web development
- Website development and administration
- Applications: Microsoft Word and Excel
- Operating systems experience: Microsoft Windows, Mac OS X, and Linux

Codewars Score



Personality Type

ISTJ: Serious and quiet, interested in security and peaceful living. Extremely thorough, responsible, and dependable. Well-developed powers of concentration. Usually interested in supporting and promoting traditions and establishments. Well-organized and hard working, they work steadily towards identified goals. They can usually accomplish any task once they have set their mind to it.

Experience

Market Cove LLC

Owner | JAN 2015 - Present

- Research, Purchase, and Sell Products on Amazon marketplace
- Provide customer support

Christ Church

Website Administration | JAN 2011 - Present

- Maintained website using Wordpress
- Provided weekly updates

9G LLC

Tech Support | JAN 2015 - SEP 2017

• Provide technical support for Mac systems, printers, and ecommerce website

Education

TrueCoders | Alpha C# Graduate

Present, Birmingham, AL

Development education, along with other marketable skills including:

- C# and ASP.NET
- Git
- ANSI SQL and Relational Databases
- HTML, CSS, JS

Christ Church School

MAY 2013, Odenville, AL

- Developed website using Wordpress
- Provide weekly updates for church website

Remarks

References and contact info for Zach Phillips are available upon request.